ASHLEY CHRISTENSEN

SUMMARY

Full stack developer with two years experience in software development. History of developing apps, improving programs and checking code. Seeking a position as a software developer, customer service engineer or technical account manager. Excellent presentation and interpersonal skills to convey technical value to stakeholders at all levels.

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Intern

Intership Program | Seattle, WA | June 2021 - September 2022

- Wrote efficient, modular and maintainable code on both front-end and back-end.
- Designed and implemented Full Stack CRUD application with front-end and back-end servers
- Shadowed team engineers to learn new skills.
- Participated in team-based project work, demonstrating ability to fill multiple roles.
- Worked in fast-paced development environment with complex project attributes.
- Worked closely with development team members to identify and remove software bugs.

Middle School Teacher; Mild To Moderate Disabiliti

San Ramon Valley Unified School District | Danville, CA | December 2020 - May 2022

- Administered tests, quizzes and other assignments to gauge students' learning and knowledge of course materials.
- Adapted teaching methods and instructional strategies to promote learning in students of differing skill levels.
- Managed consistent, learning-focused classroom environments by establishing and communicating clear objectives for students.
- Employed technology to present innovative classroom lessons and assignments.

Sales Manager

Glo Salon - Hair Extensions, Japanese Straightening, & More | San Ramon, CA | September 2016 - May 2020

- Exceeded sales goals and improved profitability by aligning sales strategies and business plans with market trends.
- Established new accounts and serviced existing accounts maintaining professional relationships.
- Performed sales consultations and educated clients on products and services.
- Prepared sales production reports for senior management.
- Maintained professional network of potential clients and business opportunities.

WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

- Portolio: https://ashley-christensen.netlify.app/
- Github: https://github.com/ashley-christensen
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ashley-christensen-339a7020a/

CONTACT

- **3** 650-518-9906
- □ ReactandFloat@gmail.com
- BRENTWOOD, CALIFORNIA 94513

SKILLS

- Expert level Javascript experience
- React, React-Native, Node.js, Express.js, PHP
- NoSQL, SQL, MongoDB, Oracle, MSSql
- HTML5, CSS3, AJAX
- DevOps: Linux, Docker, Kubernetes, Shell scripting
- RESTful Web Services, APIs, AWS, Project Management
- Version Control Systems: Git, Github, JIRA, Salesforce
- UI/UX, Technical Documentation
- Object-Oriented Programming, Data Structures
- iOS Application Development

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Full Stack Development

Advanced Javascript Web Developer Program, Seattle, WA

Honor's Graduate
September 2022

Bachelor of Arts

American Studies San Jose State University, San Jose, CA

- 2016-2020 Dean's List
- 2016-2020 Honor Roll
- 3.9 GPA
- Graduated summa cum laude December 2020

High School Diploma

Jackson Hole High School, Jackson, WY

- Graduated 2nd in Class of 150
- 4.3 GPA

June 2007